[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film tells the story of Cole Sear, a troubled boy remembered for uttering the words I see dead people.", "correct_answer": "The Sixth Sense", "incorrect_answers": ["The Grudge", "The unforgotten", "The Ring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A kunik is an intimate way of greeting that involves pressing the nose and upper lip against the skin of the other person. What group of people is this form of greeting typically associated with?", "correct_answer": "Eskimos", "incorrect_answers": ["Pygmies in Central Africa", "Native Americans in the US", "Tasmanian Aborigines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Mexican actress appeared in an uncredited role in a Friends episode in September 1994.", "correct_answer": "Lumi Cavazos", "incorrect_answers": ["Mia Maestro", "Carmen Maura", "Maribel Verdu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the subject of study of thanatology, personified in Greek mythology by Thanatos?", "correct_answer": "death", "incorrect_answers": ["plague", "birth", "grave"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is there a difference between a poltergeist and a ghost?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Robin Williams character, Daniel Hillard, in the 1993 comedy movie Mrs. Doubtfire?", "correct_answer": "Voice actor", "incorrect_answers": ["Pastry chef", "Hairdresser", "Ophthalmologist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the bartender character created and played by Jackie Gleason?", "correct_answer": "Joe", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom", "Sam", "Gus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many babies do female sloths give birth to per one pregnancy?", "correct_answer": "One", "incorrect_answers": ["Four", "Three", "Two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular female singer and actress played Elsa Morganthall Strauss-Almerson in the 1999 movie Tea with Mussolini?", "correct_answer": "Cher", "incorrect_answers": ["Tina Turner", "Barbra Streisand", "Madonna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these areas is the Black Salamander endemic to?", "correct_answer": "United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Australia", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not the name of a kitten in The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "Duchess", "incorrect_answers": ["Toulouse", "Marie", "Berlioz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no limit to how many persons with rank General can be in service in the U.S. Armed Forces at one time.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]